takvideo.com 2014-05-28

# Privacy Policy | TAKVIDEO.COM | Video Sharing

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Users Information [http://takvideo.com](http://thatfunnystuff.com/) does not store any of your personal information. Third Party Sites In order to optimize your visit, [http://takvideo.com](http://thatfunnystuff.com/) supports ads from third party sites. These sites may collect information such as your domain type or your IP address. For further information on these sites, please consult the privacy policies of the following: valueclickmedia, Nabbr , adbrite, burst media, and underdogmedia. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, contact us.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Takvideo.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Takvideo.com’s sole discretion. Takvideo.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

If you have any questions regarding the policy, you may contact Takvideo.com’s staff by using our contact form.210 Views
